He's making a list... pray you're not on it.
Santa's Slay is a comedy, fantasy, horror film directed by David Steiman.
Santa Claus is actually a demon who lost a bet with an angel,
so he became the giver of toys and happiness.
But this year the bet is off, and Santa is about to return to his evil ways.
Santa, played by Bill Goldberg.
Nicolas Yuleson, played by Douglas Smith.
Mary 'Mac' Mackenzie, played by Emilie de Ravin.
Grandpa, played by Robert Culp.
Pastor Timmons, played by Dave Thomas.
Mr. Green, played by Saul Rubinek.
Santa's Slay is a 2005 Canadian American Christmas black comedy slasher film written and directed
by David Steiman, a former assistant to Brett Ratner; Ratner served as a producer.
After a millennium of spreading Christmas joy due to losing a bet with an angel, Santa
Claus reverts to his demonic self and gives the gift of evil and fear.
The film stars Bill Goldberg, Douglas Smith, Emilie de Ravin, Robert Culp, Saul
Rubinek, Dave Thomas, Rebecca Gayheart, Chris Kattan, and Fran Drescher.
Santa's Slay was released in the United States on
December 20, 2005, by Media 8 Entertainment.
The film received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of bet, grandparent grandchild
relationship, angel, holiday, mass murder.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.